Capra Press mss., 1955-2010 LMC 2228
Lilly Library
- II. Capra Press publications
  - Sanford, John
    - View from this Wilderness, MS, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - View from this Wilderness, Page proofs and artwork, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - View from this Wilderness, Paste-ups, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
  - Savage, Mary
    - Addicted to Suicide, Artwork, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Addicted to Suicide, Corrections, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Addicted to Suicide, First MS, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Addicted to Suicide, Galleys and proofs, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Addicted to Suicide, Materials not used, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Addicted to Suicide, Page proofs, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Addicted to Suicide, Printer's MS, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Schaefer, Dennis
    - Vintage Talk, Art and photographs, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Vintage Talk, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Vintage Talk, MS, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 16-17)
    - Vintage Talk, Proofs, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 18-22)
  - Schaefer, Jack
    - Conversations with a Pocket Gopher, Galleys, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
    - Conversations with a Pocket Gopher, Illustrations, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Conversations with a Pocket Gopher, MS, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - Conversations with a Pocket Gopher, Page proofs, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Conversations with a Pocket Gopher, Paste-ups, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Conversations with a Pocket Gopher, Unbound publication, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Schoenman, Theodore
    - The Father of California Wine, galleys, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - The Father of California Wine, misc. materials, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - The Father of California Wine, partial MS, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - The Father of California Wine, xerox MS, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 17-18)
  - Scott, Mark
    - Yanks Meet Reds, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Yanks Meet Reds, Printouts, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 4-6)
  - Sloss, Radha
    - India, MS, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 22-23)
    - India, Production material, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - India, Proofs, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Ann
    - The Gifted Figure, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - The Gifted Figure, MS, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - The Gifted Figure, Photos and illustrations, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - The Gifted Figure, Proofs, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Dick
    - Condor Journal, Artwork, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Condor Journal, Clippings, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Condor Journal, Galleys, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Condor Journal, Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Condor Journal, MS, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 13-14)
    - Condor Journal, Original MS, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Condor Journal, Printer's MS, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Sommer, Robert
    - Farmer's Markets of America, Galleys, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Farmer's Markets of America, Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Farmer's Markets of America, MS, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Steele, Leighton
    - The Dance of the Minotaur, MS and artwork, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Stevens, L. Clark
    - The Steersman Handbook, Artwork, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - The Steersman Handbook, Galleys and page proofs, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - The Steersman Handbook, MS, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 20-21)
    - The Steersman Handbook, Promotional material, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Stroud, Joseph
    - In the Sleep of Rivers, Engraver's proofs, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - In the Sleep of Rivers, MS, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Stull, William
    - Remembering Ray, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Remembering Ray, Edited proofs, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
    - Remembering Ray, MS, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 7-9)
  - Sukenick, Lynn
    - Houdini, MS, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - SuZen
    - The Love Story of Sushi and Sashimi, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
    - The Love Story of Sushi and Sashimi, Proofs, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Temple, Frederic-Jacques
    - Foghorn, MS, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Foghorn, Proofs, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Vesuvius, Artwork, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Vesuvius, Misc., 1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Vesuvius, Proofs and galleys, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Terrell, John Lipton
    - The Arrow and the Cross, back cover material, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - The Arrow and the Cross, final correction pages, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Thayler, Carl
    - Goodrich, MS, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Tikkanen, Marta
    - The Love Story of the Century, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - The Love Story of the Century, MS, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
    - The Love Story of the Century, Proofs, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Todd, Edwin
    - The Neuroanatomy of Leonardo da Vinci, Proofs, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Tunick, Barry
    - Crossword Crosstalk, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Crossword Crosstalk, MS, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 12-13)
    - Crossword Crosstalk, Proofs, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 14-15)
    - Crossword Crosstalk, Text proofs, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Tway, Linda
    - Tidepools, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Van der Ryn, Sim
    - The Toliet Papers, Book design materials, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - The Toliet Papers, Clippings and miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - The Toliet Papers, Galleys, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - The Toliet Papers, Illustration proofs, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - The Toliet Papers, MS, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 20-21)
    - The Toliet Papers, Page dummies, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - The Toliet Papers, Page proofs, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - The Toliet Papers, Paste-ups, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - The Toliet Papers, Printer's MS, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Van Schaik, Frank
    - Home of the Wilson Wildcats, Proofs, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Vassi, Marco
    - Lying Down: The Horizontal Worldview, MS, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
    - Lying Down: The Horizontal Worldview, Permissions, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Lying Down: The Horizontal Worldview, Printing costs, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Lying Down: The Horizontal Worldview, Proofs, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Vinz, Mark
    - Letters to the Poetry Editor, Proofs, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - von Wiesenberger, Arthur
    - Oasis, book design materials, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Oasis, corrected galleys, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Oasis, final proofs, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Oasis, illustrations, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Oasis, miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Oasis, MS, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 10-11)
    - Oasis, MS for typesetter, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 13-14)
    - Oasis, MS paste-ups and rewrites, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Oasis, page proofs, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Oasis, Proofs, 1978 (Box 59, Folder Unknown)
  - Ward, Susan Winter
    - Yoga for the Young at Heart, First MS, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Yoga for the Young at Heart, Proofs, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 4-7)
    - Yoga for the Young at Heart, Second MS, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Wayne, Howard
    - How to Protect Your Heart from Your Doctor, Final proof, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - How to Protect Your Heart from Your Doctor, MS, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 11-15)
    - How to Protect Your Heart from Your Doctor, Proofs, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Weaver, John
    - Los Angeles, the Enormous Village, Financial documents, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
    - Los Angeles, the Enormous Village, Printer's MS, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
    - Los Angeles, the Enormous Village, Promotional material, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles, the Enormous Village, Proofs, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 9-11)
    - Los Angeles, the Enormous Village, Sources and index, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Webb, William
    - Henry and Friends, MS, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Henry and Friends, Proofs, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Weiss, Winfried
    - A Nazi Childhood, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - A Nazi Childhood, MS, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7-9)
    - A Nazi Childhood, Proofs, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - White, Jim
    - A Crow's Story of Deer, MS and artwork, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Williams, Eugene
    - Cream Dreams, Proofs, 1973 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
  - Willis, Shannon
    - Small Wonders, Draft materials and correspondence, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 9-10)
    - Small Wonders, Final proofs, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Small Wonders, Illustrations and proofs, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Small Wonders, Proofs, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 13-15)
  - Wills, Robert
    - Lawyers are Killing America, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Wilson, Colin
    - Tree by Tolkien, Artwork and design, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Tree by Tolkien, Galleys and proof, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Tree by Tolkien, MS, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Woollett, William
    - California's Golden Age, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - California's Golden Age, Illustration captions, etc., 1989 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - California's Golden Age, MS, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 19-20)
  - Yalom, Marilyn
    - Women Writers of the West Coast, Advertising, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Women Writers of the West Coast, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Women Writers of the West Coast, Galleys, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Women Writers of the West Coast, MS, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Women Writers of the West Coast, Proofs, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Young, Bob Jr.
    - From a Different Angle, A Memoir of Henry Miller, Draft, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Young, Judy
    - Celebrations, Correspondence, 1985 (Box Unknown, Folder Unknown)
    - Celebrations, Production and design costs, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Hilary the Hen, MS, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - How Molly Used Up All Her Anger, MS, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Hungry Molly's Alphabet Primer, Proofs, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Molly and Mellow Meet Seakind, Summary and proofs, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Molly's New School, Summary and artwork, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Princess Moon's Smile, Proofs, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - The Dragon Hunts, MS and artwork, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Young, Molly
    - The Dream Horses, proofs, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Young, Noel
    - California Review Issue 3, Proofs and correspondence, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Santa Barbara Architecture, Final proofs, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Santa Barbara Architecture, Photos, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Santa Barbara Architecture, Proof sheets, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Santa Barbara Architecture, Proofs for jacket, 1975 (Box 59, Folder Unknown)
    - Santa Barbara Architecture, Santa Barbara Magazine with article by Noel Young, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Santa Barbara Architecture, Second edition working copy, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Santa Barbara Architecture, Textual changes and promotional material, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Save Old State, letter to the editor, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- III. Non-Capra publications
  - Black Sparrow Press Records
    - Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 64, Folder 1-12)
    - Printing Records, 1968-1972 (Box 64, 65, Folder 13-21, 1-4)
  - Noel Young prints for other publishers
    - A Disarray of Intimacies, MS and illustrations, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - amigo, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - amigo, Galleys and proofs, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - amigo, Page proof, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - An Evening with Saroyan, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Bittersweet, Correspondence and proofs, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Bullock, Records, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Concept Twelve, Galleys and proofs, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Cream Dreams, Artwork and proofs, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Cream Dreams, Galleys, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Cream Dreams, MS, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Daisies Do Tell, Artwork and book design, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Daisies Do Tell, Page proof, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Daisies Do Tell, Second page proof, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Deep Summer Together, Correspondence and MS, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Gertrude Stein, Records and proofs, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Greenspeech, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Long Pants, Proof, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Manifests, Galleys and page proofs, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Manifests, MS, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Menashtash, Galleys, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Menashtash, LSR Material, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Menashtash, Proofs, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Misc printing, 1971-1974 (Box 66, Folder 1-4)
    - Rare Books Catalog, Records and proofs, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Reflections, Final page proof, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Reflections, Galleys and proofs, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Reflections, MS, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Ring Piece, Proofs and records, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - San Miguel Island, Proofs and galleys, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Scissors Sam, Records, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Soundings, Artwork and proofs, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Soundings, Galleys and page proofs, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Soundings, MS, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 14-16)
    - Soundings, MS typescript, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 17-18)
    - Spectrum, Engraver's proof, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Spectrum, MS, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Spectrum, Partial MS, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Stanzas, Records and proofs, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - The Chew Bunch, Records, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - The Sopping Thursday, Galleys, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - The Sopping Thursday, MS, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - The Sopping Thursday, Proofs, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - The Sopping Thursday, Records, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - The Unexplained, Correspondence and MS, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - The Unexplained, Proof, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Thomas Onetwo, Records and proofs, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Republished Capra titles
    - Hot Tubs, Artwork, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Hot Tubs, Author's galleys, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Hot Tubs, Correspondence with Random House, 1973-1975 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Hot Tubs, Dummy, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Hot Tubs, Final proof, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Hot Tubs, First proof, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Hot Tubs, Galleys and page proofs, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Hot Tubs, Large photographs, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Hot Tubs, Large proofs, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Hot Tubs, Manuscript materials, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Hot Tubs, Revised edition correspondence, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Hot Tubs, Working copy of revised edition, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- IV. Capra Press printing records
  - Capra Catalog
    - Fall catalog, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Spring catalog, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Spring catalog, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Fall catalog, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Spring catalog, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Fall catalog, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Spring catalog, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Fall catalog, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Spring catalog, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Fall catalog first draft, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Fall catalog xerox galleys and dummy, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Spring catalog, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Fall catalog, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Spring catalog, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Fall catalog, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Catalogs and proofs, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Fall catalog, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Spring catalog, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Spring and Fall catalogs, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Spring and Fall catalogs, 1987-1990 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Spring and Fall catalogs, 1991-1995 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Contracts and finances
    - January financial records, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - February financial records, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - March financial records, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - April financial records, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - May financial records, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - June financial records, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - July financial records, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - August financial records, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - September financial records, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - October financial records, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - November financial records, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - December financial records, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Royalty and sales reports, 1974-1975 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Misc. invoices, 1976-1978 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Binding and printing records, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Binding and printing records, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Publishing records, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Business records, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Contracts for Boyle, Jakes, and Powell, 1981-1989 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Financial reports, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Sales correspondence, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous printing records
    - Awards, 1956-1974 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Printed re: Henry Miller, 1961-1990 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Job tickets, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 3-6)
    - Job tickets, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 7-16)
    - Miscellaneous records, 1972-1973 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Short history and checklist of publications, 1972-1973 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Job tickets, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 19-33)
    - Titles bound by Aaron Young, 1973-1978 (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Job tickets, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 35-47)
    - Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder 48)
    - Job tickets, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 49-56)
    - Printed material and ephemera, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 57)
    - Broadside Press printer records, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 63, Folder 59)
    - Board of director's meetings minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 60)
    - Noel Young's tribute to Henry Miller for Black Messiah Magazine, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 61)
  - Promotional materials and agreements
    - Photographs of Capra Press Authors and publishers, 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 62)
    - Agreements, flyers, and press releases, 1973-1974 (Box 63, Folder 63)
    - Press history, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 54)
    - Agreements, flyers, and press releases, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 65)
    - Printed material, 1976-1977 (Box 63, Folder 66)
    - Agreements, flyers, and press releases, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 67)
    - Agreements, flyers, and press releases, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 68)
    - Printed material, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 69)
    - Spring salesman's kit, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 70)
    - Sales kits and promotional materials, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 71)
    - Printed and promotional material, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 72)
- V. Miscellaneous Capra Press documents
  - Audio/Visual Files
    - Capra Press test tape reel, 1978 (Box 58)
    - Francis Ponge interview tape, 1977 (Box 58)
  - Artwork
    - Lee Judge Comic for Christine Lee, 1981 (Box 58)